http://www.conserve-arm.com/privacy-policy-and-terms-of-use

ClientsWeb Portal LoginClient ResourcesSubmit a ComplimentConsumersManage Your AccountMobile AppConsumer ResourcesSubmit a ComplimentSubmit a ComplaintCareersHomeTwitterLinked In
Discover Why IndustriesCommercialFinancial Institution or Credit UnionGovernmentHigher EducationAbout UsHistory and MissionAccoladesLeadershipVideosThe ConServe Good Start Program®Value-Added ServicesNews & EventsPress ReleasesIndustry NewsClient ResourcesConference ScheduleConServe University® Training EventsWebinar SeriesContact UsPhone & EmailContact a Sales RepRefer a FriendProspective Suppliers
Discover Why IndustriesCommercialThird Party CollectionsFinancial Institution or Credit UnionThird Party CollectionsGovernmentThird Party CollectionsHigher EducationThird Party CollectionsAbout UsHistory and MissionAccoladesLeadershipVideosThe ConServe Good Start Program®Value-Added ServicesNews & EventsPress ReleasesIndustry NewsClient ResourcesConference ScheduleConServe University® Training EventsWebinar SeriesContact UsPhone & EmailContact a Sales RepRefer a FriendProspective Suppliers
This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the ConServe-ARM.com site and various related services (together referred to as the "site").  Continental Service Group, Inc. d/b/a ConServe, the provider of the site (referred to as "us," "we," or "ConServe"), is committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read the information below to learn the following regarding your use of this site.
You acknowledge this Privacy Policy is part of our Site Terms of Use, and by accessing or using our site, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions, or deletions shall be effective immediately upon notice thereof, which may be given by posting the revised Policy on this page. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this site and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy.
Types of Information Collected
We currently do not collect information about users of or visitors to ConServe-ARM.com. However, if you communicate to us through ConServe-ARM.com, we will collect any information you provide us.
We do not disclose your information to others. Occasionally, we may be required by law enforcement, government agencies, or judicial authorities to provide Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement or government agency investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.
User Choices on Collection and Use of Information
We may, from time to time, send emails regarding our services. In addition, if you indicated through contacts with us, that you are interested in receiving offers or information from us and our partners, we may occasionally send you direct mail or emails about services we feel may be of interest to you. Only ConServe will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your information.
Privacy Policies of Third Party Sites
Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you at this site.  Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us by sending a letter to:
Continental Service Group, Inc. d/b/a ConServe200 CrossKeys Office ParkP.O. Box 7Fairport, New York 14450Attn: Ethics and Compliance Officer
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices ofthis site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us bysending a letter to:
Continental Service Group, Inc. d/b/a ConServe200 CrossKeys Office ParkP.O. Box 7Fairport, New York 14450Attn: Ethics and Compliance Officer
Coffee's on us
Schedule an appointment and coffee's on ConServe at our first meeting.*
Call (800) 724-7500 orFind Your Sales Representative
*Valid for first time appointments only
Learn how to Recover more in 5 minutes!
Try Our Calculator
Ready to Get Started?
Call (800) 724-7500 Today or
Find Your Sales Representative
© 2019 ConServe  |  200 CrossKeys Office Park  |  Fairport, NY 14450
NMLS Number: 931208  |  http://www.nmlsconsumeraccess.org/
ConServe is an equal opportunity employer and a drug free work place.
Privacy Policy and Site Terms of Use
CareersClient LoginConsumer LoginConsumer ResourcesContact UsHome
